## Manjeet Singh

## Computer Science Engineer

Computer Science graduate seeking to use my backend development experience in a position at any good Company which could boost my knowledge and provide me with good opportunities. Possess more than 1 year of hands-on experience building and testing applications for Android and Node JS

manjeet.singh9723@gmail.com 🔀

7389438159

C-159 C-Sector Shahpura Bhopal, Bhopal, India

linkedin.com/in/manjeet-singh-144471171 in

github.com/mercenarycoder 👩

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## 1. Mern Developer & Android Developer H-card

09/2020 - 03/2021

Rhonal

A Medical Startup aimming in monitoring health of Indian citizens

- Developed Android application from scratch
- Developed Node js backend with Mysql as database from scratch
- Developed Admin Panel using React js

Contact: Raghav Patnecha (CEO, FOUNDER) - 8888110448

## Android Developer Vias Webera

12/2019 - 07/2020

Bhopal

A leading software solutions provider in Bhopal

Achievements

Developed and launched 3 Andoid Apps on playstore

Contact: Vijay Saxena (CEO, FOUNDER) - 9300131492

## **EDUCATION**

B.E. C.S.E

Oriental College of Technology, Bhopal, M.P.

06/2016 - 07/2020

C.G.P.A:- 7.87

### 12 th

St.Joseph Co-Ed School ,Bhopal,M.P

03/2014 - 04/2015

Percentage:- 82%

#### 10th

St.Joseph Co-Ed School, Bhopal, M.P

03/2012 - 03/2013

C.G.P.A:- 8.6

# PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

React JS

Node JS

Android

Java (Android)

Python

MySql (Basic)

## **PROJECTS**

- 1. GST BILLING APP ACCOUNTANT LALAJI RETAIL POS (12/2019 04/2020)
- Technologies Used : Android, Node js ,Mysql
- Description: GST BILLING APP Accountant Lalaji is complete Gst billing solution for small and Medium business owners. Retail shops, Mobile shops, Food Outlate, Restaurant, POS Billing, Optician Shops, Services, Invoice Management, SMS Bills, Print bills and Invoices, Reports and valuations all support by expert team. Simplest, Fast and Online Solution. AccordingIndia GST
- 2. H-Card Admin Panel & Android App (09/2020 - 03/2021)
- Technologies Used :- React js , Node js , Android ,Mysql
- Description: H-card is a medical software to track all the health related issues and reports of a indian citizen and providing doctor a digital way of accessing medical records and track them
- 3. Medloji (02/2020 04/2020)
- Technologies Used :- Android , Node js ,Mysql
- Description: A android app that helps buy Pharmacy, Surgicals
   Online and Get them Delivered to your Home. How to OrderSignUp
   through AppOnce registered you can browse through and search
   Medicine Upload prescriptionConfirm order and Delivery locationSit
   back and relax your Product will be delivered at your doorstep

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

1. Bronze medal in 1500 m race at nodal level

### **LANGUAGES**

Enalish

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

Coding

Cricket

Gymming